<AmItheAsshole><title title="AITA for telling a parent that their kid is weird when she pushed as to why my kid didn&#8217;t want to be her friend."><text text="My family and I have moved states. It has been a hard move especially for my oldest daughter Katty. She is in 6th grade. The areas school district has a Facebook account that parents are a part of. I introduced myself on there a while ago.&#10;&#10;&#10;We put katty on the cross country team and she has been making friends over the summer. I got a message from a parent last week, asking to met up and let the kids met. They would be in the same grade and I thought it would be a good opportunity. &#10;&#10;We went yesterday at the local pool. I met Melanie and she wouldn&#8217;t make eye contact, was very soft spoken and overall didn&#8217;t seem to be paying attention. The kids were playing while I talked to the mom. She has always been in the area and was excited her kid was getting a friend. &#10;&#10;Katty came up to me asking to leave since she wasn&#8217;t feeling well. We left early and in the car she admitted to just wanting to get away from Melanie. She explained that    Melanie freaked her out. She was very touchy, kept pushing her in the water, was whispering ( saying things under her breath), would stare at people and make comments (comparing people to bugs? I am still confused on what that means) Katty told me she was uncomfortable and doesn&#8217;t want to hang out with her again.&#10;&#10;&#10;The parent messaged me, and asked when they could do it again. I told her the girls didn&#8217;t mesh well and that we will have to decline. She then called me asking what I meant. I told her that katty wasn&#8217;t interested in hanging out since they don&#8217;t mesh together. I was trying to be polite about it.&#10;&#10;This went on for a while and she told me that they kids just needed to be around eachother more. I told her no to that. It&#8217;s went on for a while, she asked to talk to my husband which is when I snapped.&#10;&#10;I told her, no and that I was trying to be polite but your kid is weird. Melanie makes my kid uncomfortable and I don&#8217;t know what the hell is up with her but we will not have another play date.&#10;&#10;She went on Facebook and it going around about how the new family are jerks. It seems to not be going anywhere, but I am wondering if I was a dick" /></title><title title="AITA for labeling my son's school supplies and informing his next teacher they are not to be shared with his stepsister?"><text text="My son isn't back in school yet but I was contacted by his teacher for next grade asking if I had bought him all the required items and to inquire about any donated class supplies. While we were talking I told her that I had labeled my son's supplies and do not want him forced to share those with his stepsister (not my stepchild, my ex's). I also made it clear I was not counting the donated class supplies I'd be giving but just my son's personal ones. Last grade it was a constant issue and the teacher ignored me because it wasn't stated at the start of the year. So I got ahead this year.&#10;&#10;His teacher said she made a note of it and wouldn't make him share.&#10;&#10;My ex and his wife were contacted also. Her about her two kids (daughter and a younger son).. Him about our son. His wife apparently told the teacher her daughters supplies would be shared by my son and she corrected them and said she must have his own because class supplies can't substitute him the entire year.&#10;&#10;This was followed by my ex calling to say they can't afford to do this shit. He said it was bad enough finding stuff for the kids to use when my son was leaving his supplies in the cubby at school so they couldn't be used by all the kids. But now the school is saying they can't be divided between the two kids and that I'm a selfish bitch for that. He said they're family and it shouldn't be this big of an issue. I told him I was not responsible for providing for his stepkids. That if they can't afford them then it's not my problem. He told me his stepdaughter will suffer and I told him I do not care. It's not my job to make sure she and her brother are provided for and I told him that I ended up spending way more than expected on supplies last year when our son was forced to share.&#10;&#10;Ex's wife reached out and told me I should be ashamed, I should be more willing to let the sharing happening, they're siblings and belong to the same family, innocent child. I told her that if she cannot afford to buy her kids supplies she should find their dads and ask. Not expecting me, who has nothing to do with her kids, to support them.&#10;&#10;For context my son is 8, his stepsister is also 8 or literally about to turn 8 and his stepbrother is 5/6. My son wasn't willingly sharing the supplies. He was forced to by his teacher and he hated it because she did ruin some of his best supplies, especially crayons and color pencils but also his sharpener. I don't think it was intentional. It seems like she's just a rougher kid with stuff. &#10;&#10;Ex and his wife say I'm an ass and should feel so ashamed for willingly letting a child in the family suffer and for being petty about school supplies.&#10;&#10;AITA?" /></title><title title="AITA for reminding my friend that just because she&#8217;s poor, doesn&#8217;t mean I am?"><text text="I&#8217;m (20F) enrolled in the laundry program at school, where I pay a lump sum, and they do my laundry for me all year. It&#8217;s very popular at my university, and they pick it up from my dorm weekly.&#10;&#10;My friend (21F) is weirdly obsessed with this and constantly comments on it for some reason. She always comes over and sees my bag, and has some random comment to say.&#10;&#10;She&#8217;ll say, &#8220;How could anyone pay for that?&#8221; To which I always say, &#8220;Why would I ever do something I don&#8217;t want to, if I can just pay someone else to do it for me?&#8221;&#10;&#10;I&#8217;m wondering if she&#8217;s like this to everyone, because that would explain why she has few friends. Almost everyone I know uses the laundry program. Her unwanted comments make me like her less.&#10;&#10;She did it again, and was like, &#8220;What a waste of money. The laundry program is ridiculously expensive, and no one can afford that.&#8221; I simply said that I don&#8217;t find it expensive at all, and that she finds it expensive because she&#8217;s poor. I&#8217;m not, so I&#8217;ll continue paying for the program.&#10;&#10;She&#8217;s furious that I called her poor. But she is. It&#8217;s just a fact. AITA?&#10;" /></title><title title="AITA for telling my mom she was the naive one who expected her husband's son to magically change?"><text text="I (22m) was born deaf and was never a candidate for hearing aids. I was taught ASL and my mom and others in my family learned ASL too. This is the only way I could ever speak or be spoken to. I don't lip read or anything like that. My dad wasn't in my life ever. And when I was 9 my mom started dating Tom. Tom had a 10 year old son, Cole, at the time. It was pretty clear from the start that Cole was unenthusiastic about us and had no interest in learning ASL to speak to me. Tom and mom decided we should all take &quot;family&quot; ASL classes and learn together in a fun environment, which the classes they found were. Cole had to be dragged and he didn't take part willingly or eagerly. If anything he'd intentionally do things wrong and make himself do worse than he would have naturally so he was asked less.&#10;&#10;He did eventually take them seriously. My mom believed it was because he had really bonded with me and now gave a crap about communicating with me. But that wasn't it. He had a knew kid in school he wanted to talk to who was also deaf. The new guy was his motivation for learning. Cole and I never talked enough for him to be motivated to learn and he made lots of mistakes when talking to me but I noticed his ASL was perfect with his friend.&#10;&#10;It always felt weird living with someone who didn't want me around. My mom and Tom believed we'd blended eventually. I think there was some fight when Cole turned 17 and my mom and Tom wanted to go away for a weekend. I remember everyone looked so tense one morning and I was told I'd be going to stay with my grandparents for the weekend since it wasn't a great idea to leave me home alone when I couldn't hear if something was wrong. My assumption is they wanted Cole to keep an eye on me and make sure I was okay and he let them know he really didn't care what happened to me.&#10;&#10;Cole and I haven't seen each other since he moved out. My mom has asked a few times if we've met up or whatever and I'm always honest and say no. She finally asked me two or three weeks ago if things were good between Cole and me and I told her she had to have picked up on the fact he never wanted us around and wasn't interested in being good between him and me. She said she really believed that had changed once we got closer and she brought up how he took ASL more seriously. I told her it was clearly for his friend. Not me. She was clearly shocked. But brought it up again over the weekend and she told me she thought I was very naive to think Cole didn't learn ASL for both and that him being resistant at first didn't mean he didn't grow to love me. I told her she was the naive one to expect him to magically change out of nowhere. I told her if she wanted to be married to Tom that badly, it's fine. But she should accept it wasn't so perfect for me and her claiming I'm naive about Cole shows how much she wants to overlook. Mom was not cool with what I said to her. She told me I didn't need to hurt her feelings.&#10;&#10;AITA?" /></title></AmItheAsshole>