<wallstreetbets><title title="Is CBRE Corporate Real Estate Doomed??"><text text="I have some anecdotal views on CBRE having some bad mismanagement issues and know of a handful of Bay Area companies moving out of their CBRE buildings and ending their leases. Considering the macro real estate environment are these guys really effing doomed? Or why isn&#8217;t their stock tanking with the real estate market? Wtf should we expect from them next??" /></title><title title="Is Bank of the Ozarks Dominating Miami Development Financing? "><text text="Does anyone have the scoop on what's behind Bank OZK (Bank of the Ozarks) financing many / most of the real estate developments in Miami? CHISME " /></title><title title="Will DJT shit the bed next week? Full DD with updated regard speculative theory on Trump selling"><text text="Before this adderall-fueled hype train leaves the station next week, I thought i'd write up a definitive DD on the imminent DWAC/DJT merger.&#10;&#10;This DD will cover everything: fundamentals, Truth Social, ownership, dilution, Trump's holdings and lockup, the future of TMTG, regarded theories and more. You may have seen my [original comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/1bkvr48/comment/kw10fel/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;context=3) (that was stolen and reposted) with a regarded theory about Trump selling shares - **if you can't be bothered to read the full DD, then skip to the end for an updated regard theory of Trump potentially selling shares - now with new information and speculation!**&#10;&#10;Before I begin, a quick shoutout to the legend that is u/SPAC_Time. This guy is probably the most knowledgeable person about SPACs i've ever seen, and has been posting excellent information over on r/DWAC_Uncensored, a lot of which is included in this DD. I strongly recommend going and having a look at this sub as it has SO much great information on it. There's loads on there that i've not included in this DD. He's also patiently answered all my questions, so thank you king.&#10;&#10;I've been following this since the beginning, and even made an account on Truth Social to see what the bulls are thinking. Honestly some of the shit they come out with over there make the regards on this sub seem like fucking Albert Einstein.&#10;&#10;I'll also preface this by saying I have a terrible trading record, mostly crippling losses, so obviously none of this is financial advice and you should ignore everything I say. If anything is incorrect drop a comment below and i'll fix it.&#10;&#10;# Overview&#10;&#10;You probably already know what this is about, so I won't go into to much detail. Back in 2021, Trump started his own company, TMTG (Trump Media and Technology Group), which owns the social media network Truth Social. It wasn't actually Trump's idea, it was pitched to him, more on this later. The aim is to bring this to the public markets via a SPAC merger with DWAC (Digital World Acquisition Corp). Yesterday shareholders approved the merger, and it's set to complete this merge next week. DWAC has been trading publicly for a few years now, soon the ticker will change to DJT when the merger is finalised.&#10;&#10;Before I get into the finer details, here's a quick TL;DR of the bull and bear points for those who will look at this post and say &quot;i'm not reading all that&quot;&#10;&#10;# Bullish&#10;&#10;* Trump is a hype machine.&#10;* Something something woke mind virus and free speech&#10;* Truth Social is a soapbox for Trump, and everyone listens to what he says.&#10;* The run-up to the election will generate a lot of hype.&#10;* If Trump wins the election, DJT could trade on hype for a long time&#10;* In theory, if he does win the election, TMTG could become significantly more relevant, leading to an improvement in its fundamentals.&#10;* If the above happens, it's possible TMTG could bring to market their other proposed ventures - a news network and competitor to the existing streaming services.&#10;&#10;# Bearish&#10;&#10;* The fundamentals are pure dogshit&#10;* If Trump loses the election, it's all over, TMTG will probably go bankrupt.&#10;* Trump could potentially sell shares around the time of the merger.&#10;* DJT will be propped up by just hype, not adequate shareholder equity, which is volatile and unstable.&#10;* The dilution could cause a significant drop in share price if there isn't enough hype to offset it.&#10;* Trump is a serial grifter who's failed at many businesses in the past and screwed over countless customers, investors, suppliers and more.&#10;* SPACs have had a terrible track record in recent years, espeically those with poor fundamantals.&#10;* SPACs are a cheap way to go to market, with the shareholders bearing the cost of this.&#10;* TMTG has no path to profitability in the forseable future. It has not provided any updated business plans, future growth estimates, guidance or updated revenue projections. The entire company feels like it's fake, it is not acting like a normal startup would.&#10;* The other proposed ventures (news network, streaming service) are extremely expensive to get going, we're talking hundreds of millions, even billions of dollars just to get off the ground. As i'll explain later, TMTG *could* have gained the cash to do this through the merger, but unwound it, making these ventures completely unfeasible with the cash DJT will get in this merger.&#10;* Trump is desperate, and backed into a corner. He owes so much money, not just on the recent court judgements, but across his real estate porfolio as well.&#10;&#10;Right lets get into the details.&#10;&#10;# Truth Social&#10;&#10;Currently, Truth Social is the only revenue stream that TMTG has. I don't know if you've been on there at all but it's basically a hive-mind echo chamber of Trump worship.&#10;&#10;There's basically 3 types of users:&#10;&#10;* MAGA cult&#10;* Bots shilling ED pills and fake gold coins.&#10;* A small number of anti-Trump trolls, posting on every truth Trump does.&#10;&#10;I am of the opinion that Truth Social is a completely flawed concept. The concept is that Trump is trying to make a social media network, or &quot;big tent&quot;, that will be a town-square that is used by everyone - Republicans, Democrats, independents, everyone.&#10;&#10;In reality, Truth Social is a social media network hashed together from open source code to spread one-sided propaganda of a presidential candidate. Right off the bat it's a one-sided Trumpfest, and does not make any effort to include anyone other than MAGA.&#10;&#10;If Hillary Clinton made a social media network, do you think MAGA would join it? They absolutely wouldn't and this question just highlights their flawed thinking.&#10;&#10;You can say what you want about the one-sided nature that the legacy social media networks like Twitter became, but they weren't set up by a political candidate solely to give them a soapbox.&#10;&#10;There's also nearly no unique IP behind Truth Social. It's an open-source platform with no unique features. Other than (currently) the only way to hear Trump's thoughts as he takes a shit, it's worthless. It doesn't even live up to it's &quot;free speech&quot; claims, as they regularly ban people for arbitrary reasons.&#10;&#10;# Fundamentals&#10;&#10;Unsurprisingly, the fundamentals of this company are absolute dogshit. This company makes barely any revenue, and has losses in the tens of millions. I can't see how this is going to get any better after merger, and they'll have an $18m SEC fine to pay.&#10;&#10;From the balance sheet from the latest revision of the S4 in February:&#10;&#10;For the 9 months ended September 30 2023, TMTG made about $3.2m, with an operating loss on that is about $10m.&#10;&#10;TMTG claimed that in it's current financial year it projects to make about $17m in revenue, although I can't see how this projection wold be accurate. There's not been any meaningful uptick in users on Truth Social, major advertisers still avoid advertising there, and the other alleged revenue streams that they proposed early on (like a news network and streaming competitor) haven't come to fruition.&#10;&#10;# There's barely any cash backing shares of DJT&#10;&#10;The shareholder equity of DJT after the merger will be painfully low. After the merger completes, DJT will have access to the money in the trust. This money is essentially the money that DWAC sold the original DWAC shares for when it initially entered the market before it found an acquisition target (TMTG) - about 30m shares at $10/share - so the trust has approximately $300 million in it.&#10;&#10;After the merger, DJT will have to pay an $18m fine to the SEC as a result of the investigation which concluded last year.&#10;&#10;Ignore the current market value of DWAC shares for a moment. Let's look at how much cash is actually backing each share. Doing a rudimentary calculation (because we don't know exactly how much money DJT will actually get from the trust, or in-depth details of the current liabilities TMTG has): Lets say we take the full value of the $300m trust, minus the SEC fine, and the actual cash backing each share of DJT will be approximately $2.08 per share. This value could be even lower, as legal fees and other operational expenses (like DWAC expenses, and potentially costs of their lawsuits) need to be subtracted from the trust on merger before the cash is released to DJT.&#10;&#10;This low cash backing for each share is very low, it's even very low for a SPAC. In the last four years, the average cash backing per share after merge of all SPACs was about $6.67.&#10;&#10;Normally, SPACs obtain PIPE (Private Investment in Public Equity) investment during the merger process to offset low cash per share after merge. They specifically do this to ensure the SPAC can meet its operational obligations, and pay all the required costs to bring the merger to market.&#10;&#10;DWAC did have a $1.3b PIPE deal set up. This would have given the company an absolute shit ton of money, enough to fund operations for years, and fuel expansion and growth. It would have meant that each share of DJT would have been worth approximately $11.80 - pretty solid cash backing for a SPAC.&#10;&#10;However, they completely unwound this PIPE investment. My guess is because they didn't want the extreme dilution that the PIPE would have caused. The PIPE shares were not under lockup, and PIPE investors could have sold immediately on market open after the merger, destroying the share price. They were given a good deal on the shares (it was a percentage below current market value), so likely would have sold for an immediate profit. Remember this part because it works into my regarded theory later on. Spoiler alert: They weren't protecting the retail shareholders by doing this.&#10;&#10;# Ownership and dilution - what about the 1 billion shares?&#10;&#10;Currently, DWAC is mostly owned by retail. These retail shareholders are somewhat unlike &quot;normal&quot; retail shareholders in that they are insanely dedicated. Many of the estimated 400,000 retail shareholders in this will not sell for any reason. Trump could literally dump shit in their faces and they'd probably take it and hold their shares. You could say that this retail holding is stronger than in the average company&#10;&#10;After the merger this will all change.&#10;&#10;Currently the float of DWAC is about 30m shares.&#10;&#10;After the merger, the DJT float will swell to about 135m shares. The majority of these shares will be owned by Trump, currently under lockup for 6 months (more on this later).&#10;&#10;There's been lots of talk about 1 billion shares being dumped into the float after merger. This has even been widely circulated in the press, but it's incorrect.&#10;&#10;DWAC have *authorised* 1 billion shares, it hasn't *issued* them. This means that in the future, DJT could potentially issue up to 1 billion more shares without having to conduct a shareholder vote or amend the company charter. It's like 1 billion reserve shares sat there if they need it.&#10;&#10;It's actually a pretty common thing to do with IPOs and SPACs, many companies authorise shares to be issued later on to raise capital etc.&#10;&#10;In any case, if they did issue more shares from this 1 billion amount, it wouldn't be until way after the merger.&#10;&#10;There will, however, be significant dilution on merge. On business completion, up to 8,369,509 shares will be dumped into the float, given to holders of TMTG convertible notes. These shares will not be locked up like other insider shares, and can be sold immediately after merge. The holders of these notes will likely do this because they'll immediately realise a 400%+ gain. This is significant dilution, and could cause a huge drop in share price, unless insane Trump mania causes a hype rally to offset it. Much of the rest of the float is potentially (foreshadowing here) locked up, but this 8m share dump is significant.&#10;&#10;# Trump hype&#10;&#10;The hype surrounding trump is real. We've seen it many times before with DWAC - the insane rally to $175/share was surreal. It's plummet after was equally unreal.&#10;&#10;The hype has the potential to offset everything - shitty fundamentals, insane dilution and more. It's the reason DWAC has traded so far away from reality in terms of an accurate valuation.&#10;&#10;I'm sure you all saw this post about the hype, that led to you all pumping up the price of the OP's contracts by like 800% before he sold most of them:&#10;&#10;[https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/1bikpfj/these\_calls\_could\_be\_500\_baggers\_turn\_1000\_into/](https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/comments/1bikpfj/these_calls_could_be_500_baggers_turn_1000_into/)&#10;&#10;The first takeaway from the above DD is that the hype is fucking insane, and supersedes everything, can cause the share price to rocket to the moon regardless of anything else.&#10;&#10;I agree with this. It's possible that there will be a huge buying demand to offset the dilution on merge. DJT could rally to the fucking moon.&#10;&#10;The other is the theory that Trump will shill DJT and all his MAGA cult will all rush to buy in.&#10;&#10;This theory i'm not convinced on. Much of his cult have no idea how to trade shares, many of them are braindead and can barely read. And if you think that they'd buy shares anyway, think about this:&#10;&#10;Trump has literally been on-stage at rallies in front of tens of thousands of his most die-hard supporters, and directly shilled Truth Social to them and they *still* haven't rushed to join. And Truth Social is a zero-barrier, free to use social media network specifically set up for them.&#10;&#10;I personally don't think we'll see millions of MAGA pouring into the market to buy DJT. Any MAGA who already know how to trade will be holding shares of DWAC already.&#10;&#10;&amp;#x200B;&#10;&#10;# Regarded Trump selling theory - now with updates!&#10;&#10;Now it's time for the juicy stuff - the regarded speculative theory on Trump selling shares.&#10;&#10;Disclaimer: This is a regarded theory that probably won't happen, obviously i'm jumping to conclusions not necessarily found in hard evidence. If it does happen, though, I expect to be awarded a flair from the mods.&#10;&#10;It's widely understood that Trump has a lockup on his shares for six months after the merger.&#10;&#10;There is, however, a clause that undermines this.&#10;&#10;In the [latest revision of the S4](https://app.quotemedia.com/data/downloadFiling?webmasterId=90423&amp;ref=318071075&amp;type=HTML&amp;symbol=DWAC&amp;cdn=7df8a564ed5159633ce6abd5829662e5&amp;companyName=Digital+World+Acquisition+Corp.&amp;formType=S-4%2FA&amp;formDescription=%5BAmend%5D+Registration+of+securities%2C+business+combinations&amp;dateFiled=2024-02-14), filed in February, on page 42, it reads:&#10;&#10;&gt;Lock-Up. **Unless waived by Digital World prior to the Closing**, key stockholders of TMTG (including its management team) agreed to be subject to a six-month lockup in respect of their Digital World common stock, subject to certain customary exceptions, which would provide important stability to the leadership and governance of TMTG.&#10;&#10;This means that, at any time before the merger closes, DWAC could waive Trump's lockup for some or all of his shares. Further to this, they could do it before it was disclosed publicly. Trump could even sell shares for several days before it would be publicly known by DJT issuing its first 8K approximately 4 days after the merger, or Trump filing a Form 4 to disclose the sale.&#10;&#10;As mentioned in my previous comments, I theorise that Trump could potentially dump some or maybe even all of his shares, potentially even destroying the company and allowing him to walk away with billions. He could then just go back to X to continue to be able to reach an audience far bigger than on TS.&#10;&#10;Remember when Trump met with Elon earlier this month, and everyone thought it was to do with Elon donating to Trump's campaign? Wrong. I theorise that they were doing a mutually-beneficial deal:&#10;&#10;Elon agrees to ensure Trump never gets banned from X under any circumstances, ensuring he always has a soapbox.&#10;&#10;Trump agrees to return to X, giving Elon a huge bump in viewers.&#10;&#10;Trump dumps a load of his shares, pays his legal bills, makes a shit ton of money, gets a much bigger audience on X compared to Truth Social. It's a win win for both of them.&#10;&#10;**Additionally, I theorise that DWAC unwound the PIPE deal not for retail shareholder benefit, but to avoid Trump's shares from dropping in value so he could sell them at a higher price after merge. DWAC never issued a reason publicly as to why they unwound the PIPE. Unwinding the PIPE is seriously detrimental to the core of the business itself. It means significantly less cash to fund operations for a company that makes yearly losses in the tens of millions with no path to profitability.**&#10;&#10;The company will get under $300m of cash, rather than nearly $1.6bn it would have gotten with the PIPE deal + initial $300m share offering by DWAC. I'm yet to hear a reasonable explination as to why DWAC would unwind the PIPE.&#10;&#10;Something else to consider: once DJT comes to market, DWAC is essentially liquidated. It ceases to be a company, the board is dispanded and no longer work for DWAC, it's shares are swallowed up by DJT. It is **DWAC** that could waive the lockup. If shareholders were furious - would they even be able to sue a company that no longer exists? Would they even be able to join together to file an expensive lawsuit against DWAC?&#10;&#10;The counters to the above tin-foil hat theory are:&#10;&#10;&quot;But Trump wouldn't need to sell, he could just borrow against his shares&quot;&#10;&#10;I'm not convinced about this for several reasons. Firstly, what sane lender is going to lend up shares that are under lockup for 6 months. They wouldn't be able to force Trump to sell his shares to repay the debt for up to 6 months if he defaulted on the loan. Secondly, TMTG is basically worthless, with barely any shareholder equity as described above...his shares aren't worth anything and have barely any cash backing them. Lenders will want solid fundamentals before lending against shares, they aren't gonna lend him half a billion $ on shares that are propped up on hype. He recently went to more than 30 surety companies recently to try and get a loan to pay his bond, and all of them turned him down. None of them would accept real estate or non-liquid assets as collateral.&#10;&#10;[Reuters is also reporting](https://www.reuters.com/markets/deals/investors-greenlight-trumps-6-billion-social-media-deal-2024-03-22/) that he can't borrow against them due to previous terms he's agreed to:&#10;&#10;&gt;It is unclear how and when these cases will be resolved. Even if the  deal gets completed next week, Trump will not be allowed to sell any of  his shares in the combined company for six months **or borrow against them**, based on terms he previously agreed.&#10;&#10;He likely wouldn't be able to borrow against his shares even if his restriction was lifted.&#10;&#10;&quot;The board wouldn't allow it&quot;&#10;&#10;Go look at who the board of DJT is made up of: Trump, his sons and some of his closest yes-men. He basically controls the board. The DWAC board is made up of Trump yes-men as well. The fucking SEC investigation was specifically about how Trump colluded with DWAC without disclosing it publicly.&#10;&#10;&quot;Why would Trump destroy his own company?&quot;&#10;&#10;Because said company is basically worthless. It has a high share price now based on hype, but it's going to take A LOT of work to get it generating revenue and profit. When the hype dies down, the share price could plummet, reducing hes unrealised net worth. If he loses the election it's all over, and if he hasn't sold by that point he'd lose BILLIONS. Institutional investors won't be touching this, so there won't be a solid foundation of ownership.&#10;&#10;Trump looks out for himself, and he's backed into a corner. Dumping his entire holding of DJT would literally solve all of his monitary issues - court judgements, mortgage/lease payments on his properties, funding of his campaign and more.&#10;&#10;&quot;But he's screwing over his base&quot;&#10;&#10;Obviously there's a risk here, in that dumping his shares on his cult could cause a significant backlash, and he needs every vote he can get going into an election. However current DWAC shareholders are a tiny percentage of his base. If he dumped his shares on them, the majority of his base probably wouldn't even know about it. I'm not even convinced they'd turn on him either, they are literally in a cult. Remember when he said this back in 2016: &quot;I could stand in the middle of Fifth Avenue and shoot somebody, and I wouldn't lose any voters, OK?&quot;. Still rings true today.&#10;&#10;Trump is desperate. NY is about to start seizing his assets, potentially within days. I can't imagine him choosing TMTG over Trump Tower for example, especially when he could potentially liquidate his entire holding of TMTG for an immediate gain of several billion cash.&#10;&#10;# What's going to happen after merger?&#10;&#10;Honestly...who fucking knows. It could absolutely shit the bed due to dilution even if Trump doesn't sell shares.&#10;&#10;Or the hype of Trump could propel the share price into the stratosphere.&#10;&#10;EDIT: Forgot to add in the next step which will be the ticker changing from DWAC to DJT. The earliest this could happen is Monday. However an actual date hasn't been announced yet, so it could be Tuesday or Wednesday, or even later towards the end of the week.&#10;&#10;I could, and probably will be, wrong about all of this. Be sensible and don't trade this merger.&#10;&#10;Have fun regards.&#10;&#10;&amp;#x200B;" /></title><title title="The Next NYCB?"><text text="I saw this table with the regional banks most exposed to commercial real estate and the one that really popped out to me was Bank OZK. Their exposure not just to RE, but to CONSTRUCTION is enormous.&#10;&#10;Construction loans are inherently riskier than loans on existing assets because there is no income or profit to the lender until construction is complete. If they can't sell the building for what they thought they could (pretty safe to assume now that the real estate market is belly-up for offices, life sciences, hotels, and lots of multifamily), then they're not paying the full loan back. It's also harder to tell when a default is coming because there aren't regular payments that can be missed like with a mortgage. Developers also historically will keep aggressively drawing down loans to keep the lights on when they don't have any other cash coming in.&#10;&#10;OZK talks about their low LTV ratios for their loans, but assumptions have changed dramatically in the real estate world due to higher-for-longer interest rates. For example, if the cap rate on a property increases from 5% to 7%, that equates to a 28.5% decrease in value, meaning a conservative LTV ratio of 50% can very quickly climb to 70% just on that one metric.&#10;&#10;Scanning around for OZK's loans I see a bunch that look risky already.&#10;&#10;1. A $242M construction loan for a huge office tower in Denver that's about to complete but is only 4% preleased&#10;2. A $97M loan for a million sf logistics center in Glendale AZ where rents just fell by 6.9% due to so much new construction&#10;3. $265M for Nashville Yards, an office complex where Amazon announced it was pausing construction on it's own office tower&#10;4. $265M for 23Springs office development in Dallas. The only reason this development was able to move forward with construction was that Bank OZK *themselves* preleased 110,000 sf of space.&#10;&#10;OZK lent out $13.8B in 2022, the absolute top of the market for real estate, compared to just $6.6B in 2020 and $7.9B in 2021. Seems to me that the underwriting assumptions were probably way too optimistic given the current real estate recession we're in. Might take a while to play out but it feels like only a matter of time before people discover the odorous pile of excrement they have assembled.&#10;&#10;[211&amp;#37;?!?!](https://preview.redd.it/1dw0q9k0tznc1.png?width=972&amp;format=png&amp;auto=webp&amp;s=52623c55a0f2bb23626011765ebd3e4b05037bbe)" /></title><title title="What stocks will be impacted by a condo market crash in Florida?"><text text="So it looks to be happening. Condo market and maybe real estate market more generally is starting to crash in Florida.  Climate change = greater risk and higher insurance rates.  See this article.  It&#8217;s all about to crash.  What stocks will be impacted?  Insurance companies probably have this priced in, right?  How about real estate companies or banks that operate primarily in Florida?  Is this indicative of a change in other parts of the country too?&#10;&#10;https://www.floridatrend.com/article/39413/florida-condo-sales-plummet-despite-falling-prices-and-rise-in-motivated-sellers" /></title><title title="Why do people seem unconcerned about the bull run ending?"><text text=" &#10;&#10;I'm beginning to see more and more signs of an impending crash, both in the stock market and beyond. It's possible that we are heading towards a crash of unprecedented proportions. I don't want to sound like those doomsday preachers with a bell in hand who once heralded the end of the world, but I increasingly feel that way as clear signs of something brewing are evident, and people seem to be blatantly ignoring it.&#10;&#10;Let me start with the most obvious factor &#8211; everything is incredibly expensive. After analyzing numerous companies using traditional methods, I couldn't find a reasonably valued stock. The S&amp;P500 has surpassed its all-time high many times since the beginning of the year, and the chart is beginning to resemble a vertical wall. The entire market relies on NVIDIA, driven by AI and colossal expectations associated with it. The Shiller P/E ratio for the S&amp;P500 (comparing the price of the S&amp;P500 to the average annual earnings on S&amp;P500 shares for the last 10 years adjusted for inflation) is at the same level as before the crash in 1929, and if it continues to rise, it will soon reach a level close to the crash of 2000/2001. People are buying stocks without asking, &quot;at what price?&quot;&#10;&#10;Another factor is the real estate market, which has never been so inflated. I'm not an expert, but when the whole world talks about how expensive houses are, and people take out loans based on very high interest rates, thinking it won't get any cheaper, it starts to scare me. Of course, I'm not afraid that houses will become cheaper, but rather what might cause it.&#10;&#10;Next up are cryptocurrencies, whose recent rapid surges, in my opinion, signify the best indicator that the end of prosperity is near. The market is already so inflated that even the riskiest assets are gaining momentum at a very rapid pace.&#10;&#10;I would also like to mention Warren Buffett's recent annual letter. Berkshire Hathaway currently has $167 billion in cash. When asked about his plans for it, Buffett replied, &quot;I plan to wait.&quot; He added that financial markets can &quot;unpredictably stop and even disappear,&quot; as has happened in the past, and Berkshire, with its cash reserves, has the &quot;ability to respond&quot; to market downturns, which could be a &quot;great opportunity&quot; for the company. I get the impression that Buffett, too, expects a major crash but is hesitant to talk about it to avoid alarming less aware investors in his fund.&#10;&#10;Lastly, I've saved my biggest concern for the end &#8211; the specter of a third world war. As mentioned by a politician, if someone at a European summit were to mention the possibility of World War III in the past, their career would quickly come to an end. However, now it is one of the main topics at summit meetings. I fear that this could be the reason for the crash I'm talking about." /></title></wallstreetbets>